Guide to the Willard Livingstone Beard Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Collected Material, 1896-1947; Series IV
  - Re. other organizations
    - North China American School: Bulletin, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - North China American School: Pagoda, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - North China American School: The NCA, 1919,1920, 1922, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 135-136)
    - Oberlin-Shansi Association, 1933-1938 (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Miscellaneous printed and typescript material
    - Missionary circular letters, 1913-1947 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - American Fleet Souvenir, Amoy, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Journal of Educational Association of Fukien Province, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - "The Canton Government" by W. W. Willoughby, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Minutes of the First Annual Meetingf of the Mid-Fukien Divisional Council, Church of Christ in China, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Report of Foochow Youth and Religion Movement Campaign, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Letter from Peking Government University - The Anti-Religion Union, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Booklet re. Fukien Christian University, ca. 1925 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Issues of Kuliang Register, Journal of the Educational Association of Fukien Province, The Fuhkien Witness, Bulletin of the Methodist Episcopal Church in Fuhkien, Chinese Recorder, 1908-1927 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Chinese language material, including guide and ticket to bazaar in aid of the Kiangsu and Anhui Famine Relief Fund, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 141-142)
- Photographs, 1901-1956; Series V
  - Scenes and people from Foochow and Ing Tai area (Box 10, Folder 143-145)
  - Kuliang mountain resort (one photo), n.d. (Box 10, Folder 146)
  - Group and individual portraits, including missionary personnel and native Chinese (Box 10, Folder 147-149)
  - School-related, including Ponasang Girls' School, 1915, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Album re. North China American School, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Related to Foochow College, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - WLB family photos, 1912-1918 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Myron Gould Beard family photos, 1917-1956 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - WLB parents and uncles; home, family, 1901-1943 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Scenes from China, groups, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 156)
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1900-1964; Series VI
  - Biographical information, including obituaries of WLB and Mary Beard, information provided by daughter (Geraldine Beard); Commissionary Service for Phebe Beard, family tree, 1921-1964 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Framed tribute to WLB; Chinese scroll with calligraphy; Chinese language book, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Programs, news clippings, collected material, 1900-1918 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Programs, news clippings, collected material, 1925-1943 (Box 11, Folder 160)
- Compilation of Documents, 1894-1950s; Series VII
  This set of photocopied letter transcripts and photographs was compiled by Jana Jackson, wife of the grandson of Kathleen Beard Elmer. The materials are also available in digital form.
  - Introduction by Jana Jackson, compiler; transcript letters and photographs, 1894-1899 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Transcript letters and photographs, 1900-1909 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Transcript letters and photographs, 1910-1916 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Transcript letters and photographs, 1917-1921 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Transcript letters and photographs, 1922-1927 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Transcript letters and photographs, 1928-1939 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Transcript letters and photographs, 1940-1950s (Box 13, Folder 13)